Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/kurtrever (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Financial Modeling Financial Analysis Finance

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Beta Gamma Sigma Business Honor Society

Values Champion Award

Kurt Rever

Corporate Development | Private Equity | Growth Capital | M&A | Valuation | Corporate Strategy

Greater Boston

Summary

Kurt Rever is an investment professional who currently serves as a Director of Corporate Development for Verizon Communications, Inc. He has extensive experience leading M&A transactions, solving complex business challenges, and developing corporate strategies across multiple verticals.

His key responsibilities include evaluating investment targets, creating comprehensive financial models & business cases, leading large, cross-functional due diligence teams, structuring transactions, and preparing executive level presentations.

Mr. Rever earned his M.B.A. at the Boston University Questrom School of Business and holds a B.A. in Political Science & History from Boston College.

Experience

Verizon

6 years 1 month

Director, Corporate Development / M&A October 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Greater Boston

Manager, Corporate Development / M&A January 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 10 months)

Greater Boston Area

Member of Verizon's M&A team specializing in software/SaaS, mobility, autonomy, IoT, telematics, robotics, & field service management.

Manager, Corporate Development / M&A & Corporate Strategy (Verizon Connect)

July 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 6 months)

Greater Boston Area

Responsible for M&A activities and business strategy for Verizon Connect, a leading global provider of vehicle telematics & mobile workforce solutions for service-based businesses of all sizes delivered as software-as-a-service (SaaS).

Verizon Connect is a division of Verizon Communications, with more than 3,500 dedicated employees in 15 countries. Verizon Connect is guiding a connected world by automating, optimizing and revolutionizing the way people, vehicles and things move and interact. Verizon Connect's full suite of industry-defining solutions and services put innovation, automation and connected data to work for customers and help them be safer, more efficient and more productive.

Associate, Corporate Development / M&A (Verizon Connect)
April 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 4 months)
Greater Boston Area

Sheehan Family Companies Corporate Financial Analyst February 2013 - April 2017 (4 years 3 months)

Greater Boston Area

Analyzed financial performance of all business units and evaluated special opportunities for executives of the Sheehan Family Companies.

Achievements:

- Lead teams in the creation of dynamic pro-forma financial models to test a range of acquisition and expansion scenarios;
- Prepared quarterly covenant calculations and compliance documents for senior lender;
- Measured and tracked sales, accounts receivable, inventory, and leverage trends on a monthly basis to improve operations and increase cash flow;
- Created and compiled corporate and operating-level financial reports for quarterly shareholder meetings including detailed reports on budget variances, operating expenses, and profitability;
- Organized the biannual budget process for all 20 operating units and worked with general managers to produce comparative financial statements and accurate budget request presentation packets;
- Assisted the corporate accounting team and external auditors with year-end procedures;
- Provided day-to-day accounting support to unit level accounting managers to ensure timely and accurate completion of financial reporting

Axiom Capital Group, Inc.

5 years 9 months

Senior Associate

June 2010 - January 2013 (2 years 8 months)

Boston, Massachusetts

Axiom Capital Group, Inc. is a Boston-based merchant-banking firm focused on privately-owned middle market companies.

Achievements:

- Evaluated investment opportunities based on collateral, cash flow, projected IRR, and proposed deal structure to provide recommendations to senior partners;
- Analyzed client firms and portfolio companies for past and future performance and conducted financial due diligence on acquisition targets;
- Supported the creation of Axiom Partners, LP, a \$20MM special opportunities fund with a focus on hard money loans and distressed debt workouts with responsibility for cash management and fund accounting;
- Prepared expert witness testimony with Managing Director on the role of private equity investors and industry norms and standards;
- Hosted meetings between clients and prospective lenders;
- Appointed interim controller of portfolio company Aces, LLC, a 20-unit Little Caesars franchise in southwest Virginia with responsibility for cash management, AR, AP, bank reporting, and shareholder reporting;
- Appointed VP of Administration for portfolio company Independence HomeCare, Inc. with responsibility for all business operations (financial reporting, payroll, HR, licensing, compliance, cash management, AR, & AP) where I collaborated to grow the business from 0 to 700+ billable hours per week;

Associate

September 2007 - June 2010 (2 years 10 months)

Boston, Massachusetts

Achievements:

- Wrote detailed offering memorandums for presentation to prospective lenders and investors;
- Assisted senior team members in the development of financial models;
- Managed deal closings and communications between counter-parties and attorneys;
- Provided turnaround consulting and recommendations to companies in the waste management, hospitality, fitness, and fast food industries;

- Counseled clients on compliance and financial covenant issues;
- Devised business plan to develop Independence Home Care, Inc., a non-medical home care startup;
- Co-created the Independence University employee training program to educate new hires on company policies, rules, and regulations.

Summer Intern

May 2007 - September 2007 (5 months)

Boston, Massachusetts

Achievements:

- · Conducted market research on target industries;
- Worked as part of a deal team to facilitate closings and coordination of deal documents;
- Led planning discussions on the state of capital markets, foreign and domestic policy, and macroeconomics.

UNHCR, the UN Refugee Agency Intern in the Protection, Policy, and Legal Advice Section October 2006 - December 2006 (3 months)

Geneva Area, Switzerland

Achievements:

- Monitored deliberations and reported on outcomes of the 3rd Regular Session and 4th Special Session of the Human Rights Council;
- Assisted Senior Liaison Officer to prepare the UNHCR's Assistant High Commissioner's statement at the 4th Special Session of the HRC;
- Edited, compiled, and distributed confidential comments by the UNHCR to the UN Human Rights Treaty Bodies;
- Wrote feedback reports to UNHCR field offices after attending 13 meetings of the Committee Against Torture;
- Attended numerous UN and UNHCR briefings, meetings, and lectures on various topics including address by outgoing UN Secretary General Kofi Annan.

Education

Boston University Questrom School of Business Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Finance, General

Boston College

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Political Science & History

Pinkerton Academy